{
    "key": "Quiz",
    "name": "Quiz 2",
    "description": "A second simple quiz",
    "items": [
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (B)?",
            "choices": ["Apple", "Bear", "Camera", "Dog"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (A)?",
            "choices": ["Aviation", "Balloon", "Cow", "Desk"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (E)? What is the correct answer (E)?",
            "choices": ["Alchemy", "Bastion", "Creative", "Door", "Egress"],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (B)?",
            "choices": ["Apple", "Bear", "Camera", "Dog"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (A)?",
            "choices": ["Aviation", "Balloon", "Cow", "Desk"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (B)?",
            "choices": ["Apple", "Bear", "Camera", "Dog"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (A)?",
            "choices": ["Aviation", "Balloon", "Cow", "Desk"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (E)? What is the correct answer (E)?",
            "choices": ["Alchemy", "Bastion", "Creative", "Door", "Egress"],
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (B)?",
            "choices": ["Apple", "Bear", "Camera", "Dog"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the correct answer (A)?",
            "choices": ["Aviation", "Balloon", "Cow", "Desk"],
            "answer": 0
        }
    ]
}
